<idea-plugin>
    <id>com.adbconnect.plugin</id>
    <name>Remote ADB Connector</name>
    <version>1.0.5</version>

    <vendor email="support@adbconnect.com" url="https://github.com/adbconnect/remote-adb-connector">
        ADBConnect
    </vendor>

    <description><![CDATA[
        <h2>Remote ADB Connector</h2>
        <p>
            Connect to Android devices attached to a remote Windows ADB server
            from your Linux Android Studio instance — with a single click.
        </p>
        <h3>Features</h3>
        <ul>
            <li><b>One-click connection</b> — enter the Windows IP, click Connect, done.</li>
            <li><b>Automatic device discovery</b> — detects USB devices on the remote server.</li>
            <li><b>TCP mode switching</b> — automatically runs <code>adb tcpip</code> on the remote device.</li>
            <li><b>Continuous monitoring</b> — watches for disconnections and auto-reconnects.</li>
            <li><b>No shell scripts</b> — everything is implemented natively in Kotlin.</li>
            <li><b>Per-process ADB server switching</b> — never modifies your global environment.</li>
        </ul>
        <h3>How it works</h3>
        <p>
            The plugin connects to the ADB server running on your Windows machine,
            discovers USB-connected Android devices, switches them to TCP mode,
            and connects them to your local Linux ADB server — all automatically.
        </p>
    ]]></description>

    <change-notes><![CDATA[
        <h3>1.0.5</h3>
        <ul>
            <li>Added selective per-device connection options (WiFi and USB) in the Available Devices list</li>
            <li>Implemented dynamic port forwarding for USB mode to support multiple concurrent USB connections without conflicts</li>
            <li>Enabled continuous Windows server background monitoring alongside local Linux connection tracking</li>
        </ul>
        <h3>1.0.3</h3>
        <ul>
            <li>Added interactive "Help" button in the tool window showing setup commands for exposing the Windows ADB server</li>
            <li>Updated documentation with network setup guides and visual mockups</li>
        </ul>
        <h3>1.0.2</h3>
        <ul>
            <li>Added light and dark themed plugin icons for Marketplace and IDE Plugin Manager</li>
        </ul>
        <h3>1.0.1</h3>
        <ul>
            <li>Initial release</li>
            <li>Full connection workflow: discover, prepare, connect, monitor</li>
            <li>Auto-reconnect on device disconnection</li>
            <li>Persistent settings</li>
            <li>Tool window with real-time status</li>
            <li>Custom branding and icons for sidebar and plugin marketplace</li>
        </ul>
    ]]></change-notes>

    <!-- Platform dependency — works with any IntelliJ-based IDE -->
    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <!-- Tool Window -->
        <toolWindow id="Remote ADB"
                    factoryClass="com.adbconnect.plugin.ui.RemoteAdbToolWindowFactory"
                    anchor="right"
                    secondary="false"
                    icon="/icons/toolWindowIcon.png"/>

        <!-- Notification Group -->
        <notificationGroup id="Remote ADB Connector"
                           displayType="BALLOON"/>
    </extensions>
</idea-plugin>
